foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
it's an honor to be recognized as part
of the Asia trusted life agents and
advisors Awards
Manulife Vietnam is truly humble to be
named the insurance company of the year
as the first born owned life insurer in
the market we are extremely proud of the
pioneering role our company has played
in the local Industries development
we are also proud of how our efforts
have contributed
to Vietnam's economic prosperity and the
healthier and more resilient people
of course we couldn't have done this on
our own
in many ways this award further
validates the hard work and passion of
our sixty thousand strong team of
advisors
and that of our employees and Bank
partners be it to bank Tech Home Bank
and Saigon Commercial Bank
as a company
we remain committed to promoting the
professionalism of our agency Force
the digital transformation of our
business
along with delivering best-in-class
services and experiences
like many of you we have continued to be
tested by the pandemic
yet it's at times like these that the
true value of insurance also shines
through
these Awards continue to be a
celebration of our industry
and the passion we all share
for empowering
physical and financial well-being in the
community
I'd like to thank the Asia advisors
Network
Asia Insurance review limra and the
panel of judges for recognizing
manualize contribution and Leadership
I'd also like to congratulate all the
nominees and winners as part of this
year's Awards
let's together
continue to stay focused on building a
better industry to better the world
come on
thank you
[Music]